[{
		"id": "1",
		"question": "Javascript is _________ language.",
		"options": {
			"a": "Programming",
			"b": "Application",
			"c": "None of These",
			"d": "Scripting"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": "2",
		"question": "JavaScript is ______ Side Scripting Language.",
		"options": {
			"a": "Server",
			"b": "ISP",
			"c": "None of These",
			"d": "Browser"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": "3",
		"question": "JavaScript is designed for following purpose -",
		"options": {
			"a": "To Style HTML Pages",
			"b": "To add interactivity to HTML Pages",
			"c": "To Perform Server Side Scripting Operation",
			"d": "To Execute Query Related to DB on Server"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": "4",
		"question": "JavaScript is can be written -",
		"options": {
			"a": "directly into JS file and included into HTML",
			"b": "None of these",
			"c": "directly on the Server Script",
			"d": "Both (a) and (b)"
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": "5",
		"question": "JavaScript is an ________ language.",
		"options": {
			"a": "compiled",
			"b": "interpreted",
			"c": "Both (a) & (b)",
			"d": "None of above"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": "6",
		"question": "JavaScript Code can be called by using",
		"options": {
			"a": "RMI",
			"b": "Triggering Event",
			"c": "Preprocessor",
			"d": "Function / Method"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": "7",
		"question": "The type of a variable that is volatile is",
		"options": {
			"a": "Volatile variable",
			"b": "Mutable variable",
			"c": "Immutable variable",
			"d": "Dynamic variable"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": "8",
		"question": "A hexadecimal literal begins with",
		"options": {
			"a": "00",
			"b": "0x",
			"c": "0X",
			"d": "Both 0x and 0X"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": "9",
		"question": "When there is an indefinite or an infinity value during an arithmetic value computation, javascript",
		"options": {
			"a": "Prints an exception error",
			"b": "Prints an overflow error",
			"c": "Displays Infinity",
			"d": "Prints the value as such"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": "10",
		"question": "Which of the following is not considered as an error in JavaScript?",
		"options": {
			"a": "Syntax error",
			"b": "Missing of semicolons",
			"c": "Division by zero",
			"d": "All of the mentioned"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	}
]